[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":32586,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":114428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":6327,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":120763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":7576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":128344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3554,"trial_type":"feedback ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":131902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":137248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1635,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":138888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and t hen add  the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":9497,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":148388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1775,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":150167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":153673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":980,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":154655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3761,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":158418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"C orrect!  3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":44126,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":202548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":206439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1181,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":207622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub >6</sub>  3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4714,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":212338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1004,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":213345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract  6 to get  your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":216249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":999,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":217251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3148,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":220402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":730,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":221134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":224074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":715,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":224792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":10794,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":235596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3  is its o wn inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":23939,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":259538,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":264614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1060,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":265676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub> 6</sub>?  <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":268849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":856,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":269707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":272652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":885,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":273539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":277027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the id entity u nder +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":861,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":277890,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":280962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3139,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":284104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operatio n can si mply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7696,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":291802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +< sub>6</s ub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":14333,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":306136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":8442,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":314582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2145,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":316729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":319408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":7842,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":327251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<su b>6</sub >? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":332318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":333671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2797,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":336470,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1298,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":337771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice ques tion wit h feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":8518,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":346292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":349679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":990,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":350672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":354390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":359458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":363454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3185,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":366643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":370934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":38625,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":409561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"four plus one equals five which is less than nine","explanation_history":["foi","four plus one equals five which is less than nine"],"response_history":["5"],"rt":23472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":433039,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"eight plus four is twelve subtract nine is three","explanation_history":["eight plus fou ","eight plus four is twelve m","eight plus four is twelve so","eight plus four is twelve subtract nine is three"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1216012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1649057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":true,"explanation":"two numbers must add to nine to be subtracted from nine and equal zero","explanation_history":["two numbers must add to nine to be subtracted from nine and equal zero"],"response_history":["9"],"rt":33621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1682694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1686488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 und er +<sub >9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":8464,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1694954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1699998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"six plus three equals nine subtracted from nine equals zero","explanation_history":["six plus three equals  nine su br","six plus three equals nine subtracted form nin","six plus three equals nine subtracted form ni","six plus three equals nine subtracted form n","six plus three equals nine subtracted form ","six plus three equals nine subtracted form","six plus three equals nine subtracted for","six plus three equals nine subtracted fo","six plus three equals nine subtracted from nine equals zero"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":18365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1718368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"two can be added to numbers that are less than nine","explanation_history":["two plus three","two plus thre","two plus thr","two plus th","two plus t","two plus ","two plus","two plu","two pl","two p","two can be adde d to num bers that t","two can be added to numbers that do not equa","two can be added to numbers th","two can be added to numbers t","two can be added to numbers that are less than nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":29420,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1747795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"three can be added to numbers that are smaller than nine","explanation_history":["three w","three can be added to numbers that are smaller than nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":38332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1786134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"m ulti","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers","explanation_history":["five can be added and u","five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers bes","five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers be","five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers b","five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers ","five can be added and subtracted to equal all numbers"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":27388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1813527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"some numbers cannot be made by adding with six and subtracting with nine","explanation_history":["no"," n","some  numbers can ","some numbers cannot be made by adding with six and subtracting with nine"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":51684,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1865220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":8139,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1873363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n=n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 + n","1 + ","1 +","1  ","1"," 1+n=m","1+n=n"],"rt":29785,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1903152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n=n","explain":true,"explanation":"something added to any number is equal to n","explanation_history":["somtehin","something added to 0 is equal to n","something added to ","something added to any number is equal to n"],"response_history":["x+","x","1+x=n","x+1=n","x+=n","x+0=n","x+0n","x+nn","x+n=n"],"rt":75150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1978314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"numbers that have inclusive and exclusive multiples with n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["numbers that have inclusive multiples with n","numbers that have inclusive amultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive anmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive andmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and multiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and emultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and excmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclumultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclusmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclusimultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclusivmultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and exclusivemultiples with n","numbers that have inclusive and  exclusi ve multiples with n"],"rt":54521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2032853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":8435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2041296,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":7114,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2048416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14- 0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":7730,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2056150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"a divisor of n must be multiplied by something else to get n","explanation_history":[" d"," ","a divisor must be p","a divisor must be multiplied by something else to get n","a divisor  must be multiplied by something else t o get n","a divisor of must be multiplied by something else to get n","a divisor of  must be multiplied by something else to get n","a divisor of n must be multiplied by something else to get n"],"response_history":["True"],"rt":32307,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2088462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":41539,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2130008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please e xplain i n words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"it depends on the number and whether or not it is 0","explanation_history":["it epe","it ep","it e","it depends on the number and whether or not it is 0"],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":109672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2239689,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":23522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2263218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14 -0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1743,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2264963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"28","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["28"],"rt":2202,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2267171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2269744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"math for elementary teachers, Algebra 2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["math for elementary teachers, Algebra 2"],"rt":15895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2285643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it "],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":9192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2294842,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2301289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something f rom this  HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2305514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2309299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definite ly","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":5163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2314465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2316584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4834,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2321421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["ni","no"],"rt":3372,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2324795,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"interesting, thank you!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["interesting, thank you!"],"rt":6385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2331184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]